hello everyone this is ey on E censored
Supernatural Bible changes on YouTube
and today is Saturday January 20th
2024 and I want to let you know about my
latest book that's been published and
available on Amazon it's called crafty
devilish
witchcraft with a
cauldron all those are new words in the
King James Bible we have over we have
thousands of Chang scripture right now
and it's horrendous the King James Bible
and all other English Bibles and bibles
across the Earth in different languages
are supernaturally changing preparing
for the Antichrist and coming when World
satanic system the reign of the
Antichrist everything is being inverted
the King James Bible now has grammar
errors nonsense verses doctrinal errors
new people words erased words added
emoticons punctuation and grammar errors
and on and on it goes in this small book
5.75 in x 6 in I include I'm going to
show you in just a minute two verses per
page that have been altered in the King
James
Bible this particular book covers the
changes that relate to anything crafty
devilish or witchcraft now in the Bible
like Spirit
cooking it's
diabolical but let me go ahead and show
you this
this is um on Amazon and you can buy it
there today I show over 400 Bible verses
over five excuse me over
400 that have been supernaturally
changed and these new verses have
mistakes in them and they have new words
such as crafty devilish horish cauldron
Apothecary piss oracles Necromancer go a
whoring and more
and that's what I'm going to show you in
this book it's really easy just to show
anybody the changes by opening up any
page of this particular book and to have
somebody read these verses and to give
you a response back and anyone with eyes
to see should be able to discern the
changes let me go ahead and show
you um some of these the contents of
this book so you can see for
yourself and and here is um this is what
the inside looks like has two verses on
each page and this says First Kings
22:53 for example says yet I have left
me 7,000 in Israel all the knees which
have not bowed unto Baal and every mouth
which hath not kissed him do you
remember that Isaiah 8:9 and when they
shall say unto you seek unto them that
have familiar spirits and unto Wizards
that peep and that mutter should not a
people seek unto their God a question
mark than a small f for the living to
the
dead do you see the
changes here's two others First Kings
619 and the Oracle he prepared the house
within to set there the Ark of the
Covenant of the
Lord Isaiah 9:20 and he shall snatch on
the right hand and be hungry and he
shall eat on the left hand and they
shall be satisfied they shall eat every
man the Flesh of his own
arm First Kings 628 and the King said
unto her what aileth thee and she
answered this woman said unto me give
thy son that we may eat him today and we
will eat my son
tomorrow James 2:15 if a brother or
sister be naked
and destitute of daily
food and on on it goes like here is uh
I'll read two more First Kings 631 and
for the entering of the Oracle he made
doors of Olive Tree the lentil and side
post were a fifth part of the wall James
2:19 thou believest that there is one
God thou doest well the devils also
believe and
tremble the word demon and demons no
longer exist in the King James Bible all
replaced with devil and
Devils this is witchcraft these changes
are happening through black magic
through frequency meant to deceive as
many souls to hell as possible to
worship the
Antichrist and what's happening is that
Jesus
Christ is being demoted in the Bible
he's being called all types of
blasphemies and the enemy is pretending
that he is
God deceiving
people it's unbelievable but it's
absolutely happening and you need to
wake up in Jesus name I encourage you to
search out the matter pray and fast and
seek the Lord open up your Bibles do
your own research as I've always
implored you to
do Jesus Christ is the word of God we
know that from John 1:1 in Revelations
the Bible is supernaturally changing
while the church
sleeps it's unbelievable but it's
obvious on every single page there are
problems and errors on every single page
of the
Bible it's time to wake up in Jesus name
let me go back
to this information give me a
minute hold
on so here we have
the um the information on Amazon and
then I want to show you my other books
here that I've written that I encourage
you to read especially the first two on
the left because these give a excellent
Foundation of what's happening but then
any of these other books are a wealth of
information um this particular book has
over 400 this one that I've been telling
you about has over 400 scripture verses
that have been altered that are obvious
if you open up scripture you don't even
have to be educated learning learned in
scripture to see that there's a problem
with scripture today because of the
grammar errors the nonsense verses the
language the imagery that's now in Bible
is ungodly and
wicked it's been polluted by the words
of the wicked one now we know in 2
Thessalonians 2 that when the Antichrist
comes you to come with lying signs and
wonders and he's going to pretend that
he is God remember that and speak great
great offenses great blasphemies against
God and he will declare himself as God
this is what's happening today in
scripture do you have eyes to see what's
happening now I also want to go back
here and just share with you so these
are the books that I've written great
information for you to share to research
which I always encourage you to do these
are my latest books these are all
smaller books 5 by S
5.75
by6 and each of these small books are
just filled with scripture changes on
these various topics from Aliens to the
impostor you know impostor meaning the
one who's pretending that he is God the
counterfeit to the pandemic and plagues
you know the whole thing that we went
through the past two years are recorded
in scripture
essentially College Mak and looking
glasses that's a whole another segment
of changes we see in scripture related
to education and then castles Duke and
unicorns a whole royal mythological
agenda being dropped into scripture I
hope and I pray that these tools are
useful for you as you're searching out
the matter I pray God blesses you and
protects you and he sets your course on
the right track because we know that
we're living in perilous times and we
know that
all of this is happening according to
Bible
prophecy be strong and courageous do not
fear or be dismayed for the Lord your
God is with you wherever you go until
next
time